Branden Ng

Front-End Web Developer Melbourne, VIC

linkedin.com/in/brandendaniel in

github.com/BrandenDaniel 😱

Web Portfolio - branden.vercel.app

 ${\cal A}$ brandendanielng@gmail.com

J 04 32 375 587

Experienced front-end web developer with a fiery passion for transforming static wireframes into interactive, beautifully spaced websites. Throughout my journey, I have crafted outstanding websites that have wowed clients and peers, boasting professionally structured and understandable code. I am currently learning React.js and API integrations.

Experience

LeasePLUS Group - SafeCode

Sept. 2022 - Present

Front-end Web Developer

Melbourne CBD, VIC / Hybrid

SafeCode, a LeasePLUS subsidiary, creates novated leasing and salary packaging interfaces for individuals and businesses. With 100,000+ users, they cater to diverse clients and governments across Australia.

- Maintain proprietary leasing/salary packaging software with clean & structured front-end code. (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery)
- Maintain and manage LeasePLUS's websites (salarypackagingplus.com.au, Leaseplus.com.au)

LeasePLUS Group - SalaryPackagingPLUS

Accounts Officer - salary deductions receivable & payable

Apr. 2022 — Sept. 2022 Melbourne CBD, VIC

Arcadian Digital &

Sept. 2019 - Feb. 2020

Junior Front-end Web Developer

Melbourne CBD, VIC

As a bespoke digital and marketing agency, Arcadian delivers tailored solutions to organisations of all sizes.

- · Collaborative work with project managers/senior developers, producing smart and intuitive solutions
- Build and structure WordPress reusable child themes
- · Build and maintain company's own WordPress plugins and themes

Bebble Media &

May. 2018 - Jun. 2019

Junior Front-end Web Developer

North Laverton, VIC

A small digital agency in West Melbourne with in-house designers and developers. Specialising in WordPress, they assist small business owners in expanding their ecommerce and online presence.

- · Collaborate with web/graphic designers to reach mockup standards
- Integrations of plugins + customisation of plugins to suit client's specifics
- Manipulation of software styles (i.e plugins, themes) exact to design mockups

Tech Stack & Skills Interests & Hobbies JavaScript | React | HTML | CSS | Sass ETFs & Index Funds Personal Finance Tech jQuery | Bootstrap | Git | API integration Critically Acclaimed Films | Youtube Work **Personal Projects** 2023 My Web Portfolio & 2023 MySalPack (employee portal) & JavaScript | jQuery | Sass | Blazor | Bootstrap React | JavaScript | HTML Sass Print Strategy Management & 2019 YouTube Clone & 2023 JavaScript | jQuery | WordPress Bootstrap CSS React | Material UI | Rapid API Axios Sass Kader Boot Co. 🔗 2019 Cryptoverse & 2023 JavaScript | jQuery | WordPress Rapid API Bootstrap React | Redux | Axios Sass Ant Design

Education

Udacity

Front End Web Developer Nanodegree

Oct. 2017 - May 2018

Team Treehouse

May - Aug. 2017

Online

Front End Web Development Track

Online

Melbourne, VIC

RMIT University

Jul. 2016 — Apr. 2017

Completed 48 credits towards a Bachelor of Information Technology

Relevant Courses Included:Web Programming

User-centered Design